What you can't see can hurt you.
Black Water is a adventure, drama, horror film directed by David Nerlich.
Based on true events, Grace, her boyfriend Adam, and her younger sister, Lee, are on
holiday in Northern Australia when they decide to take a tour down a river.
As they drift into a swamp, their boat suddenly capsizes.
Stranded in the flooded swamp, the three tourists must figure out what to do to
survive as they realize they are being watched through the black water.
Lee, played by Maeve Dermody.
Grace, played by Diana Glenn.
Adam, played by Andy Rodoreda.
Jim, played by Ben Oxenbould.
Pat, played by Fiona Press.
Black Water is a 2007 Australian-British horror film written and
directed by Andrew Traucki and David Nerlich.
The film, an international co-production of Australia and the United Kingdom, is set in the mangrove
swamps of northern Australia, and stars Diana Glenn, Maeve Dermody and Andy Rodoreda.
Inspired by the true story of a crocodile attack in Australia's Northern Territory in December 2003, a pregnant woman, along with her
boyfriend and her sister, takes a boat tour of a mangrove swamp, where they are terrorized by a ferocious saltwater crocodile.
The film explores themes of australia, river, crocodile, tourist, swamp.
The tone is dark and emotional.